# leva Kaleginienė

## From seller to developer



I've been working in IT industry for about six years and now my career goal is to retrain from seller to FrontEnd developer. I'm sure, that such ambitious goal is a proof of extremely high motivation and willingness to learn a lot.

## Contact



+370 677 28390



ieva.kaleginiene@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/ieva-kaleginiene



github.com/kaleginiene



Vilnius, Lithuania

## Software skills

HTML, CSS, SASS JAVASCRIPT NODE.JS VUE.JS REACT **PHOTOSHOP** 

I have some experience working with developer platforms Digital Ocean, MS Microsoft Azure and Firebase. Also, i have some skills writing SQL code.

## Working skills

**TEAMWORK** QUICK LEARNER **LEADERSHIP PLANNING** PROJECT MANAGEMENT

Working as a Sales manager I gained strong set of communication, team working, negotiation and problem solving skills, which is going to be advantageous for FrontEnd developer career.

## Experience

Sales manager

TELIA LIETUVA, AB

2016.09 - present

In this job position my duties are: Selling IT and Mobility services for medium and large B2B clients. Attending meetings with clients and project management: constructing budget and

timelines

Virtual assistant

VaMigle

2020.05 - 2020.09

I was working on a startup's process management. My duties were: SalesForce implementation, creating processes and training sales people. Also, working with Web Designer and FrontEnd

developer was one of my responsibilities too.

Baltnetos komunikacijos, UAB

Account manager

2015.05 - 2016.09

In this job position my duties were: selling IT services to potential and existing B2B clients, attending meetings with client, managing portfolio of over 400 clients, project management:

constructing budget and timelines.

Administrator - Sales manager Domus Lumina, UAB

2014.12 - 2015.05

2012.07 - 2014.12

Roller Blinds, louvers etc. products salon administration, orders management, organizing

timetables for foremen group.

Insurance consultant

PZU Lietuva, UAB DK

In this job position my duties were: communication face to face and over the phone with B2C clients, contracts extension and upselling, settlements monitoring, search of potential clients.

### Education

#### Code Academy

#### FrontEnd Course

2020.03 - 2020.12

A 9-month course of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Responsive design, Bootstrap, SaSS, Node.js, GIT. Besides, I've gained strong skills of React. I know how to use Hooks (useState, useEffect, useContext), storybook and styledcomponents extensions. Furthermore, I've learned coding with Vue.js framework. After finishing this course, I can create websites with high-quality code written and connect it with MySQL databases. As a playground, we used development platforms such as Digital Ocean, MS Microsoft Azure and Firebase.

#### Vilnius **Gediminas** Technical University

#### Economics Bachelor, Business management specialization

2011 - 2015

Economic theory, Economic governance, E. business, E. logistics, E. Marketing, Innovative business Investment, Personal financial economics, Financial decisions, The financial market, Microeconomics, Macroeconomics, Public finance

## Courses

#### Code Academy

#### Digital skills training

3 month course of: WebDesign, HTML & 2020.09 - 2020.12 CSS basics, WordPress, SEO, eCommerce

#### Coursera

#### Modern JavaScript: ES6 Basics

8 hours of JavaScript basics, where I've 8 hours learnt JS major features of ES6.

#### Johns Hopkins Web development University

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap course.

2020.08 - 2020.10

#### Women Go Tech

## Atrask technologijas

3 months

3 month course about IT industry, UX/UI Coding, IT project management, Agile

Basics.